Hi, my name is Ateesh and my name is Piyush Kerk and together we are bringing an awesome course
on Node.js. Whenever somebody wants to get started with Node.js, there are three prominent
questions that everybody asks. What is Node.js? How should I learn this into this modern age?
And once I learn this, how can I implement this into professional and production grade projects?
This course address exactly the same thing from foundations to behind the scenes to projects
everything is covered in this course. This course is not just a deep dive into Node.js,
but we will also work into things like creating our own web servers using core HTTP module of Node.js.
And there are so many such fun things that we are going to do. Not only that, we are also going to
address how Node.js becomes an integral part in building production grade application with
all the modern tools that you have seen around. Things like Express, Drizzle, Doc,